you know most people here at the bottom
right here were thinking that this that
the dollar was going to break down and
the Bull Run was about to begin and what
does it do it counter counter trade wins
right while everyone thinks the dollar
is going to break down it pumps up and
it's pumping like a [__] this is
the bottom of the range this is the top
of the range you know the dollar looks
bullish right now which is overall not
good for the market you know so that is
not what you want to see for a the big
bull market that everyone's preparing
for so obviously once you start to break
down that's when you're really in my
opinion in a confirmed bull run like the
the euphoric beautiful part of the bull
run where you make stupid money easily
in crypto